Guide to the Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1886-1987; Series IV; 3; (5 boxes)
  - Biographical information
    - Notorious at 90 [documentary]
      - Agreement, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 597)
      - Outline, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 598)
    - Press release, 1931 Apr 29 (Box 19, Folder 599)
    - Profiles
      - Alive and Well and Living in New York, 1984 Oct (Box 19, Folder 600)
      - Overseas Press Association Bulletin, 1982 Feb 1 (Box 19, Folder 601)
      - This Week magazine See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 856
      - Woman's Wear Daily See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 856
    - Resumés, 192?-[77] (Box 19, Folder 602-03)
    - Who's Who Publications
      - Correspondence, 1957-85, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 604)
      - Galley proofs and clippings, [1953?]-75 (Box 19, Folder 605)
  - Bookmarks, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 606)
  - Budget calculations, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 607)
  - Business cards, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 608)
  - Calendars, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 609)
  - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 610)
  - Catalogs, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 611)
  - Clippings
    - Baltimore, 1947, 1980, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 612)
    - Health concerns, 1985, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 613)
    - Jewish business dynasties, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 614)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1960-71, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 615)
    - Mencken, H. L., 1958, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 616)
    - Obituaries, 1966-76 (Box 19, Folder 617)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 618)
    - Paper collectibles, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 619)
    - Patton, Oliver J., 1968 Aug 28 (Box 19, Folder 620)
    - Profiles of friends, 1979-86 (Box 19, Folder 621)
    - Publishing, 1978-86 (Box 19, Folder 622)
    - Theater, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 623)
    - War Recreation Commission, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 624)
    - Weirton Steel Company, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 625)
    - Miscellaneous subjects, 1924-86, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 626)
      See also: Oversize, Box 28, folder 856
  - Dance card [Johns Hopkins University] and gift card removed from book [ Proposal under Difficulties by John Kendrick Bangs], 1908 (Box 19, Folder 626a)
  - Democratic Women's Council of Philadelphia, Luncheon in Honor of Mrs. Franklin Delano Roosevelt, invitation and cards, 1943 Oct 13 (Box 19, Folder 627)
  - Dietary menus, [1965-66?] (Box 19, Folder 628)
  - Fabric souvenirs, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 629)
  - "Gifts made to Mrs. Nathan," list, 1951-64 (Box 19, Folder 630)
  - Graphic works
    - Baltimore, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 631)
    - Kroll, Leon. "Leo Ornstein at the Piano"
      See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 857
    - Miscellaneous, 1964, 1971, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 632)
  - Gutman Family
    - Cemetery plot map, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 633)
    - Family history by Joel Gutman David Hutzler, 1967 Dec 23 (Box 19, Folder 634)
    - Family history notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 635)
    - Family trees, 1979, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 636)
    - Joel Gutman & Co.
      - Catalog, 1888-89 (Box 19, Folder 637)
      - Christmas Eve speech, 1904 Dec 24 (Box 19, Folder 638)
      - Clippings, 1903, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 639)
      - Stockholders list, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 640)
      - "What She Wore," promotional booklet, 1899 (Box 19, Folder 641)
    - Notebook, Louis K. Gutman, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 642)
    - Obituary, Joel Gutman, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 643)
    - Wedding notebook, Ida Newberger and Louis Gutman, 1886 Mar 17 (Box 20, Folder 644)
    - Wedding notice, Ida Newberger and Louis Gutman, 1886 Nov 20 (Box 20, Folder 645)
    - Will, Ida Newberger Gutman, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 646)
  - Handkerchief case, with note (Box 20, Folder 647)
  - Identity and membership cards, 1925-68, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 648)
  - Introduction cards, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 649)
  - Inventory of belongings, 1972, 1974, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 650)
  - Jury duty certificate, 1957 Jan 15 (Box 20, Folder 651)
  - Licenses, 1925, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 652)
  - List of letters sent to Actors Fund sale (Box 20, Folder 653)
  - Lyric sheet, Raindrops Keep Fallin' On My Head, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 654)
  - Notebooks, re: personal possessions, 1934, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 655)
  - Notes
    - Addresses and telephone numbers, 1975-87, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 656)
    - Miscellaneous subjects, 1964-77, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 657)
  - Oral history deed of gift, Goucher College, 1981 Oct 12 (Box 20, Folder 658)
  - Package tags, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 659)
  - Passports, 1924-67 (Box 20, Folder 660-61)
  - Prescription, 1949 Jul 8 (Box 20, Folder 662)
  - Printed materials
    - After War Messages to the American People: Kings, German and American (Box 20, Folder 663)
    - American Jewish Historical Society Conference Announcement, 1985 Jun (Box 20, Folder 664)
    - The American Revolutionary Era Symposia Program, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 665)
    - Auction catalog pages, 1973, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 666)
    - Barbizon Plaza Promenade, 1971 Apr (Box 20, Folder 667)
    - Book catalogs, 1976, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 668)
    - "A Bridge Opens to Brooklyn," exhibit souvenir, [1983?] (Box 20, Folder 669)
    - The Chesterian, 1927 Nov (Box 20, Folder 670)
    - Civil War Roundtable of New York: Its History and Membership, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 671)
    - Dance program, Anna Pavlowa, 1921 Nov 19 (Box 20, Folder 672)
    - The Diagonal, 1920 Feb (Box 20, Folder 673)
    - Drama in the High School, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 674)
    - Editorial Comment on the Tournament and the Little Theatre Movement..., 1923 (Box 20, Folder 675)
    - The Empire State Voter, 1956 Oct (Box 20, Folder 676)
    - F. E. Compton and Company Catalog, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 677)
    - The Festival Theatre Review, [1926?] (Box 21, Folder 678)
    - Goucher College
      - Alumnae directory, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 679)
      - Commencement program, 1978 May 28 (Box 21, Folder 680)
      - Goucher College Weekly, 1916 Jan 13 (Box 21, Folder 681)
      - Goucher Quarterly, 1980-84 (Box 21, Folder 682-83)
    - Harmony Circle program, 1929 Nov 27 (Box 21, Folder 684)
    - Irish World and American Industrial Liberator
    - Legislation Won in the Equal Rights Campaign, 1921-1929, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 685)
    - Marx and Engels on Reactionary Prussianism, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 686)
    - The Masses, 1917 Jul (Box 21, Folder 687)
    - Menckeniana, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 688)
    - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors exhibition brochure, 1923-24 (Box 21, Folder 689)
    - New Mexico, 1960 Dec (Box 21, Folder 690)
    - New York magazine, 1971 Dec 20 (Box 21, Folder 691)
    - New York Historical Society 80th Anniversary Patron list, 1984 Nov 19 (Box 21, Folder 692)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1985 Apr 14 (Box 21, Folder 693)
    - New York World's Fair
      - "The Fair, the City, the Future" issue of New York Times Magazine
      - See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 858
      - Souvenir map, 1964-65 (Box 21, Folder 694)
    - Otis Elevator Co. brochure, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 695)
    - Pathways, 1985 Jan (Box 21, Folder 696)
    - Playbills
      - Anatol, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 697)
      - The Iceman Cometh, 1946
      - Strange Interlude, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 698)
      - Street Scene, 1947
      - Tartuffe, 1937 Sep
    - Playbooks [list], 1896-1924 (Box 21, Folder 699)
    - The Play Pictorial, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 700)
    - Preserving the Design for Americans, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 701)
    - Show Business, 1952 Mar 17 (Box 21, Folder 702)
    - Suffolk Museum, "The Mount Brothers," exhibition catalog, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 703)
    - Theatre Arts, 1916 Nov (Box 22, Folder 704)
    - Theatre Arts Monthly, 1924 Jan (Box 22, Folder 705)
    - Tourism guide, Hungary, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 706)
    - Tourist materials, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 707)
    - True Comics, "Little Flower", 1941 (Box 22, Folder 708)
    - The Ultimate Power bookjacket, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 709)
    - A Virginia Gentleman's Library, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 710)
    - Voter's Digest, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 711)
    - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin
      See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 858
  - Receipts, 1938-86, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 712)
  - Recipes, annotated, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 713)
  - Restaurant menus, 1943-46 (Box 22, Folder 714)
  - Savings account passbook, 1985-86 (Box 22, Folder 715)
  - School course handouts (Box 22, Folder 716)
  - School reports, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 717)
  - Scrapbook 1, 1925-36 (Box 22, Folder 718-36)
  - Scrapbook 2
    See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 859
  - Sheet music
    See: Oversize, Box 28, folder 860
  - Stock certificate, 1922 Feb 9 (Box 22, Folder 737)
  - Telephone notebook [blank], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 738)
  - Transistor radio instructions, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 739)
  - Travel souvenirs, 1968, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 740)
  - Wallet, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 741)
  - Wedding newspapers
    - Lill Blum - Maurice Fleischer, 1911 Jan 25 (Box 22, Folder 742)
    - Adele Gutman - James Nathan, 1912 Feb 20 (Box 22, Folder 743)
- Photographs, 1865-1989; Series V; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  Series V, Photographs, is arranged alphabetically by subject. AGN = Adele Gutman Nathan
  - Albums
    See: Oversize, Box 29, folders 860-63 and Box 30, folders 864-65
  - Animals, 1922, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 744)
  - Awards, 1917, 1955, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 745)
  - Blinky the Pony, ca. 1895 (Box 23, Folder 746)
  - Cone, Etta and Claribel with Gutman Family, ca. 1895-1928 (Box 23, Folder 747)
  - AGN in Cone Family living room reproduction, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 748)
  - Eleanor's party and Goucher College series, 1981 Oct (Box 23, Folder 749)
  - Excursions
    - Atlantic City, ca. 1908 (Box 23, Folder 750)
    - Mt. Washington, New Hampshire, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 751)
    - Naples, Maine, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 752)
    - Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 753)
    - Twin Mountain, New Hampshire, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 754)
    - Wernersville, Pennsylvania, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 755)
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1900-20 (Box 23, Folder 756)
  - Family portraits of friends
    - Lindsay family (Box 23, Folder 757)
    - Lisberger family, n.d.
    - Lyons family, 1951-52
  - AGN with Friends, 1951-85, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 758)
  - Friends of AGN, 1951-63, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 759)
  - Golden Spike Centennial, [1969] (Box 23, Folder 760)
  - Groups of people, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 761)
  - Gutman children
    - Adele and Elsie, album pages, ca. 1900 (Box 23, Folder 762)
    - Adele, Elsie and Joel, ca. 1889-1904 (Box 23, Folder 763)
  - Gutman family, ca. 1900 (Box 23, Folder 764)
  - Gutman house, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 765)
  - Gutman, Ida N., ca. 1895-1920 (Box 23, Folder 766)
  - Gutman, Louis, ca. 1865-1920
  - AGN with Indian Tribe, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 767)
  - Interiors, 1909, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 768)
  - Katzenstein, Sarah Frank, 1870 (Box 23, Folder 769)
  - Kaye, Elizabeth Gutman
    - Exhibitions, ca. 1955-72 (Box 23, Folder 770)
    - Portraits, ca. 1915-68 (Box 23, Folder 771)
      See also: Oversize, Box 31, folder 866
    - Travel series - Sarasota, Florida, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 772)
  - Kaye, Walter, ca. 1930-40 (Box 23, Folder 773)
  - Larsson, Pamela Patton and family, 1951-78 (Box 24, Folder 774)
  - Museum of the City of New York: communications exhibit, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 775)
  - Nathan, Adele Gutman
    - Portraits, ca. 1900-89 (Box 24, Folder 776-78)
    - Wedding portrait, ca. 1914 (Box 24, Folder 779)
  - Newberger family, ca. 1850 (Box 24, Folder 780)
  - Patton, Gerri and husband, 1940, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 781)
  - Personal property, 1938, 1972, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 782)
  - Sculptures of AGN, 1925, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 783)
  - Tennis, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 784)
  - Theatrical productions, 1920, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 785)
  - Travel series: France, Italy, Algiers, 1924-25 (Box 24, Folder 786)
  - Vatican City, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 787)
  - Unidentified people, ca. 1870 (Box 24, Folder 788)
  - Miscellaneous subjects, 1945, 1951, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 789)
- Elizabeth Gutman Kaye Papers, 1883-1972; Series VI; 1; (2 boxes)
  Series VI, Elizabeth Gutman Kaye Papers is divided into alphabetically arranged subseries.
  - Clippings
    - Artists, 1954, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 790)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1959, 1961, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 791)
    - Exhibition announcement and reviews, 1954-69, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 792)
    - Interview, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 793)
    - Marriage notices, [1912] (Box 25, Folder 794)
    - Obituaries, 1971 Apr (Box 25, Folder 795)
    - Profiles of Elizabeth Gutman Kaye, 1917-49, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 796)
    - Performance notices and reviews, 1915, 1925, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 797)
  - Correspondence
    - Aaron, May Todd, 1954-55 (Box 25, Folder 798)
    - Casella, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 799)
    - "G"-"H" general, 1915-32 (Box 25, Folder 800)
    - Indy, Vincent, d', [1927?]-28 (Box 25, Folder 801)
    - "M"-"W" general, 1914-71 (Box 25, Folder 802)
    - Unidentified letters, 1947-61, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 803)
    - Greeting cards, n.d.
    - Empty envelopes and stamps, 1938, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 804)
  - Exhibitions
    - Guestbooks, 1956-67 (Box 25, Folder 805)
    - Publicity, 1947-72, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 806-07)
    - Scrapbook
      See: Oversize, Box 31, folder 866
  - Graphic Works
    - Cows, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 808)
    - Portrait of Elizabeth Gutman Kaye by Olaf Olson
      See: Oversize, Box 31, folder 867
  - Notes
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 809)
  - Performances
    - Advertising flyers and brochures, 1921-30, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 810)
    - Publicity and programs, 1915-41, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 811-12)
  - Personal Papers
    - Biographical sketches, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 813)
    - Business cards, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 814)
    - Drawings, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 815)
    - Estate evaluation, 1971 Jun 16 (Box 25, Folder 816)
    - Eulogy for Walter Kaye, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 817)
    - Exhibition flyer: G. Sciltian [signed], 1966 (Box 26, Folder 818)
    - Kaye, Walter, vital information, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 819)
    - Memorial notice, 1971 Jun 20 (Box 26, Folder 820)
    - Notebook of sale of possessions, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 821)
    - Notice of probate, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 822)
    - Passenger list: R.M.S. Queen Mary, 1961 Nov 30 (Box 26, Folder 823)
    - Poem about Elizabeth Gutman Kaye, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 824)
    - Receipt, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 825)
    - Travel pass, 1950 Aug (Box 26, Folder 826)
    - Travel souvenir, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 827)
    - War Camp community service medal, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 828)
    - Wedding songbook, 1911 Feb 15 (Box 26, Folder 829)
    - Wills, 1968, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 830)
  - Photographs
    - Dubrovnik, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 831)
    - Italy, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 832)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 833)
  - Printed Materials
    - Art Student's League Newsletter, 1971-72 (Box 26, Folder 834)
    - "Longfellow's Poem on Amalfi" [leaflet], 1883 Feb 18 (Box 26, Folder 835)
    - Programs, 1968, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 836)
    - The Trouble Buster, 1918 Oct 19 (Box 26, Folder 837)
  - Radio Programs
    Adventures in Art
    - Clipping, 1939 Nov 8
    - Scripts, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 839)
    - Art for All and All for Art (Box 26, Folder 840)
    - Conversations in Art script, 1938 Jun 11 (Box 26, Folder 841)
  - Writings
    - Alice in Songland, scripts, typewritten, with letter, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 842)
    - Articles, printed columns and photocopies, 1925-57, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 843)
    - The Magic Pussy-cat, typescript, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 844)
    - [My Education], holograph, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 845)
    - A Norse Tale, typescript, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 846)
    - Patches of Light
      - Advertisements, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 847)
      - Books, 1961
      - Review, 1961 Jan 5 (Box 26, Folder 848)
    - Poems, typescript and manuscript (Box 26, Folder 849)
    - Susie's Big Day
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 850)
      - Workbook with typewritten text, sketches and paintings (Box 26, Folder 851)
- Oversize, 1850-1984; 8; (5 boxes)
  Oversize contains materials from Series I, II, IV, V, and VI.
  - WRITINGS
    - Books
      Victorian in Bohemia
      - Research material: clippings, 1968 Dec 1
    - Columns
      - St. Nicholas, magazine advertisement, 1943-44 (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 852)
    - Pageants
      Niagarama
      - Clippings [photocopies], 1861, 1886 (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 853)
      - Magazine article, Holiday, 1961 Jun (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 853)
      - Poster, n.d. (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 853)
      - Recorded background music, audiodiscs (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 853)
      - Weirton Steel Company
        1942 Labor Day Celebration
        - Photographs, 1942 (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 854)
        - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin, 1942 Sep (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 854)
        - 1943 Labor Day Celebration
          - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin, 1943 Sep 3 (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 854)
        - 1944 Labor Day Celebration
          - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin, 1944 Sep (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 854)
    - Shorter Works
      - Song lyrics, n.d. (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 855)
  - PROJECTS
    - National Association of Manufacturers
      - Congress of American Industry program, 1941 Dec (Box Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 855)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Awards
      - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin, 1944 Apr (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 856)
    - Biographical Information
      - Profiles
        - This Week magazine, 1948 Aug 29 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 856)
        - Woman's Wear Daily, 1982 Mar (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 856)
    - Clippings
      - Miscellaneous subjects, 1961, 1964 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 856)
    - Graphic Works
      - Kroll, Leon "Leo Orenstein at the Piano," [photoreproduction, signed], 1921 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 857)
    - Printed material
      - Irish World and American Industrial Liberator, 1926 May 15 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 857a)
      - New York World's Fair
        - "The Fair, the City, the Future" issue of New York Times Magazine, 1964 Apr 19 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 858)
      - Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin, 1934-40, n.d. (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 858a)
    - Scrapbooks
      - Scrapbook 2, 1949-50 (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 859)
    - Sheet Music
      - Sheet Music, 1900-40, n.d. (Box Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 860)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Album 1, ca. 1850-60 (Box 29, Folder 861)
    - Album 2, ca. 1890 (Box 29, Folder 862)
    - Album 3, ca. 1910-30 (Box 29, Folder 863)
    - Album 4, ca. 1910-20 (Box 29, Folder 864)
    - Album 5, ca. 1905-15 (Box 30, Folder 865)
    - Album 6, ca. 1885-1905 (Box 30, Folder 866)
    - Kaye, Elizabeth Gutman: portraits, ca. 1915-40 (Box 31, Folder 867)
    - Nathan, Adele Gutman: portraits, ca. 1923-45 (Box 31, Folder 867)
    - Newberger family, ca. 1880 (Box 31, Folder 867)
  - ELIZABETH GUTMAN KAYE PAPERS
    - Exhibitions: scrapbook, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 868)
    - Graphic Works
      - Portrait of Elizabeth Gutman Kaye by Olaf Olson, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 868)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.5; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 32 contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator.
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 32, Folder 869)
  - Box 2, folder 46 (Box 32, Folder 870)
  - Box 4, folder 106 (Box 32, Folder 871)
  - Box 4, folder 122 (Box 32, Folder 872)
  - Box 4, folder 123 (Box 32, Folder 873)
  - Box 5, folder 131 (Box 32, Folder 874)
  - Box 8, folder 194 (Box 32, Folder 875)
  - Box 8, folder 195 (Box 32, Folder 876)
  - Box 8, folder 196 (Box 32, Folder 877)
  - Box 8, folder 198 (Box 32, Folder 878)
  - Box 8, folder 199 (Box 32, Folder 879)
  - Box 8, folder 212 (Box 32, Folder 880)
  - Box 9, folder 244 (Box 32, Folder 881)
  - Box 9, folder 248 (Box 32, Folder 882)
  - Box 9, folder 257 (Box 32, Folder 883)
  - Box 9, folder 260 (Box 32, Folder 884)
  - Box 9, folder 284 (Box 32, Folder 885)
  - Box 10, folder 298 (Box 32, Folder 886)
  - Box 10, folder 303 (Box 32, Folder 887)
  - Box 10, folder 306 (Box 32, Folder 888)
  - Box 11, folder 341 (Box 32, Folder 889)
  - Box 11, folder 348 (Box 32, Folder 890)
  - Box 11, folder 363 (Box 32, Folder 891)
  - Box 12, folder 394 (Box 32, Folder 892)
  - Box 12, folder 405 (Box 32, Folder 893)
  - Box 12, folder 411 (Box 32, Folder 894)
  - Box 12, folder 412 (Box 32, Folder 895)
  - Box 14, folder 445 (Box 32, Folder 896)
  - Box 14, folder 461 (Box 32, Folder 897)
  - Box 15, folder 482 (Box 32, Folder 898)
  - Box 16, folder 510 (Box 32, Folder 899)
  - Box 22, folder 718 (Box 32, Folder 900)
  - Box 22, folder 719 (Box 32, Folder 901)
  - Box 22, folder 720 (Box 32, Folder 902)
  - Box 22, folder 721 (Box 32, Folder 903)
  - Box 22, folder 722 (Box 32, Folder 904)
  - Box 22, folder 723 (Box 32, Folder 905)
  - Box 22, folder 724 (Box 32, Folder 906)
  - Box 22, folder 725 (Box 32, Folder 907)
  - Box 22, folder 726 (Box 32, Folder 908)
  - Box 22, folder 732 (Box 32, Folder 909)
  - Box 22, folder 734 (Box 32, Folder 910)
  - Box 22, folder 735 (Box 32, Folder 911)
  - Box 22, folder 736 (Box 32, Folder 912)
  - Box 24, folder 794 (Box 32, Folder 913)